Everyone, attack!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
I'm not sure you're gonna keep it.
I don't know what not.
I'm afraid of my fear.
I'm in the back of my head.
I'm in the same way.
I'm in the
same way.
I'm in the same way.
Here is the most beautiful place.
I'm so happy with my body.
What if I'm feeling, I don't want this?
I'm so happy with my heart.
I'm so happy with my eyes.
You'll see it in my house.
I'm so happy when you
feel like I'm feeling.
I'm so happy with my feelings.
I'm so happy with you.
So A-N-D-S.
I wanna always do with you.
I'm giving you everything I have.
How many did we lose?
14 of us died.
Oh my god!
And we still got 25 floors to go.
25 more floors?
How the hell are we even
gonna make it that far?
Kirito, what are you...
An immortal object?
Commander Heathcliff, what's going on?
I think I got the answer to that.
Reason why the Commander's HP never hits
yellow is because he's
protected by the system.
You know, ever since day one, something's
always bugged me about this whole thing.
I was always wondering,
where is he hiding while he watches us
and controls everything in this world?
Well, the answer's pretty simple.
It's basic psychology.
In fact, it's so simple
every kid knows it.
There's nothing more boring than
watching someone else play an RPG.
Is there, Akihiko Kayaba?
Just for my curiosity's sake, would you
mind telling me how you figured it out?
The first time I knew something
was up was during our duel.
Remember when you turned the tables on me?
That move was way too fast.
Yes, I thought so.
It was a mistake to think that
would go unnoticed by you.
But you were so strong and so fast,
the only choice I had was to
engage the system's assist mode.
Yes, I am Akihiko Kayaba.
And now that my identity's been revealed,
it should come as no surprise that I
am the final boss on the top floor.
So the strongest player in the whole
game ends up being the final boss.
Kind of cliche, isn't it?
Actually, I kind of like that angle.
One thing's for sure,
I always thought you'd be the one
standing before me at the very end.
You know, dual wielding is a rare skill,
the kind that's only given to the
player with the fastest reaction time.
He is the hero of this story, the one
who rises up to challenge the Demon King.
But you, the power you've
displayed exceeded my expectations.
I guess these unexpected twists and turns
are what makes MMORPG
so thrilling to play.
Our loyalty, our hope.
Paralysis.
Kirito!
What's the plan now, huh?
Huh?
You gonna kill everyone here
and cover it up or something?
Oh, God, no.
That wouldn't be sporting
of me, now would it?
No, I have a better idea.
I'm going to head for the top floor
and wait for all of you there.
I'll be inside the Ruby Palace.
It's a shame I have to
leave you all so soon.
I've spent lots of time
developing the Knights
of the Blood Oath and other elite players.
Oh, well.
You're all strong, so I'm sure
you'll reach me, eventually.
But before I go...
Kirito, I feel you deserve some kind
of reward for discovering my identity,
so I'll give you a chance.
Chance for what?
To fight me one-on-one,
right here, right now.
Oh, and my immortality
will be deactivated.
Defeat me and you clear the game,
and all of the players will be
able to log out from this world.
No strings attached.
What do you say?
Don't do it, Kirito.
I don't like it.
We should fall back.
Oh,
my
God.
I have to.
Okay then, let's finish it. Kirito.
I'm sorry, I can't run away
if it means ending this.
You better not die, you hear me?
No, I'm gonna win.
I promise I'm gonna end this world.
Okay, I believe in you, Kirito.
Kirito! Don't! Kirito!
Hey, Gil.
Thanks for supporting all the
players in the game since day one.
Yeah, I knew.
You act like you're all about the money,
but I know you spent
every penny you had on
helping the intermediate players level up.
Klein?
I'm sorry I bailed on you that day.
I think about it all the time.
Dammit, Kittito!
Don't you apologize!
Don't you dare apologize now!
I won't accept it!
I'll never accept it until we're on the
other side and you're buying me dinner,
goddammit!
You got it.
See you on the other side.
If it's okay, I have a final
request to make. What is it?
I'm not planning on going down easy.
So if I die today,
I want your word that you'll fix
it so Asuna doesn't kill herself.
As you wish.
No, Kirito, that's not fair!
You can't do that!
It's not fair! No!
This isn't some in-game duel.
It's a fight to the death.
That's fine with me.
Because I'm going to kill him.
He can block whatever I throw at him.
Because he designed the
dual-wielding skill.
and he knows all its combos.
I have to beat him with my own power
without using the sword skills.
Faster.
I gotta go faster! Oh!
I'm sorry, Asuna.
Please, keep living.
Game over, Kirito.
Asuna, Asuna, you can't, you can't be.
I'm sorry.
Goodbye.
Now that was a surprise!
I'm sure I never programmed a way for
players to neutralize their own paralysis.
I guess sometimes these
things just happen.
Hmm?
It's over now.
I believe in you, Kirito.
Not yet.
We did it, didn't we?
PHONE RINGS
On November 7th at 2.55pm,
the game has been cleared.
Repeat, the game has been cleared.
Where am I?
Kitty-dough. Kitty-dough.
I'm sorry.
I guess I ended up dying, too.
Dummy.
Where are we?
Do you know?
A stunning view, isn't it?
Akihiko Kayaba.
At Argus headquarters,
the SAO mainframe is in a room
five floors below street level.
and right now it's deleting
all the data from its drives.
In about ten minutes, everything in
this world will disappear forever.
And all the players?
What happens to them?
You don't have to worry about them.
The 6,147 players who survived the game up
to now were logged out a few seconds ago.
And what about the 4,000 people who died?
What about them?
They'll never return.
In any world, real or virtual,
once you're dead, you're gone.
Why?
What's the point?
Why did you do this?
That's a good question.
It's been so long I've
forgotten the reason.
Isn't that strange?
Even before I developed a system for the
full-dive environment, I dreamed of this.
A castle in a world that wasn't governed
by earthly laws and restrictions.
I poured my life into
making that world a reality.
I created this world,
and I got to see something that surpassed
anything I could have imagined for it.
My steel castle, floating in the sky.
I don't remember how old I was
when I became obsessed with it.
I wanted to leave the earth,
to fly to that castle.
I wanted that more than anything
else, for as long as I can remember.
You know what, Kirito?
I want to believe it's still out there.
That somewhere in some other world, my
castle is still standing, taller than ever.
Yeah, maybe it still is.
Before I forget, congratulations on
clearing the game, Kirito, Asuna.
Well then, I should
probably get going now.
Guess this is goodbye.
This isn't goodbye at all!
We're gonna be together
when we finally disappear.
So we're gonna be together forever.
Hey, you never told me your real name?
Would you please tell me before we go?
Kazuto
Kazuto Kirigaya And
last month, I turned 16.
Kazuto Kirigaya.
So you're younger than me, huh?
My name is Asuna Yuki.
I'm 17 now.
Asuna Yuki.
Sorry.
I swore.
I promised I'd save you, get you
back to the real world, but I...
I couldn't.
It's okay.
I'm happy I got to meet you, Kazuto, and
to be with you, and to live with you.
This is the happiest I've
ever been in my whole life.
Thank you for that, and I love you.
I love you so very much.
Oh, my God.
Oh, Sue.
Oh, I'm sorry.
It's just the reality that the reality is.
I've been looking forward
to seeing the future.
The world's infinite.
Even if it's a dream.
Even if it's too late.
It's always, always.
Next time, return.